哦,天哪
Oh, my God.
以赫弗齐芭的力量
By the power of Hephzibah,
我强迫你摧毁！
I compel you to oblivion!
哦，一个女孩
Oh, a girl.
小恶魔
第一季第一集
十三年后
你需要一根针，克里斯蒂娜
You'll need a needle for that one, Christina.
那是囊肿  - 你才是囊肿
That's cystic. - You're cystic.
你怎么知道我需要什么？
How do you know what I need?
因为我是你的妈妈，妈妈们最清楚
Because I'm your mother, and mothers know best.
哦，你说得对，妈妈  你最清楚
Oh, you're right, Mother. You do know best.
我很高兴你在学年中间
I'm so glad you moved us to a new town
把我们搬到了一个新的城镇
in the middle of a school year
所以我要和一群全新的孩子一起
so I get to restart seventh grade
重新上七年级
with a whole new group of kids.
听着，我知道这并不理想
Look, I know it's not ideal,
但是——但是不要因为经济问题怪我，好吗？
but--but don't blame me for the economy, okay?
我得去工作的地方  - 妈妈！
I got to go where the work is. - Mom!
走人行横道，你这个小鬼！
Use the crosswalk, you little gremlin!
哇，幸好你妈妈反应
Whew, you're lucky your mom's got the reflexes
像只该死的猎豹
of a goddamn cheetah.
我要走完剩下的路
I'm walking the rest of the way.
我再也受不了你了
I can't stand another minute with you.
你确定你没事？
Are you sure you're okay?
是的，我很好 - 怎么了？
Yeah, I'm fine. - What's going on?
你觉得有点烦躁吗？ - 什么？
You feeling fussy?  - What?
你的小玫瑰花蕾疼吗？
Your little rosebuds tender?
告诉我  - 停下来！
Tell me. - Stop it!
恶心，妈妈！ - 让我感受一下
Ew, Mom! - Let me feel.
- 你离我远点！ - 让我感受一下！
- Get off of me! - Let me feel them!
嘿，会痛吗？ - 再见！
Hey, does this hurt? - Goodbye!
不要忘记新学校的规则！
And don't forget new school rules!
假设每个人都是杀人犯，直到事实证明并非如此！
Assume everyone is a murderer until proven otherwise!
克里斯蒂娜？
Christina?
我最喜欢的演员都被取消了。
STUDENT 1: All of my favorite actors got cancelled.
之后我说，“是的，妈妈，
STUDENT 2: And I was like, "Yes, Mom,
我爱我的追随者胜过爱你”
I do love my followers more than you."
那是新来的女孩吗？
STUDENT 3: Is that a new girl?
哦
Ooh.
米德尔顿初级中学
建于1795
我们不再是种族主义者了！
嘿，伙计
Hey, guy.
介意我和你共享这个储物柜吗？
Mind if I share this locker with you?
嘿，抬头！
Hey, heads up!
再见，你个混蛋！
Bye, you motherfucker!
接住你了，小家伙
Gotcha, little one.
嗯，你好  - 你好
Um, hi. - Hi.
我想这条 30 条腿的友好蜈蚣是你的
I believe this 30-legged friendly centipede is yours.
哦！哦，是的，谢谢 是的
Oh! Oh, yeah, thanks. Yeah.
你是新来的，对吧？嗯
You're new here, right? Uh-huh.
我是本尼根，自封的学校迎新员
I'm Bennigan, resident self-appointed school greeter.
啊，嗨
Oh, hi.
我是克丽丝  - 嗨
I'm Chrissy. - Hi.
你知道蚰蜒的学名吗
Did you know the technical name of the house centipede
是Scutigera ...-Coleoptrata
is Scutigera... -Coleoptrata.
是的 -哦，你知道！
Yeah. Oh, you knew!
我完全知道
I totally knew.
书呆子！
Nerds!
所以今晚在康科德派克废弃的塔可城堡
So there's, like, this party tonight
有个派对
at the abandoned Taco Chateau on Concord Pike.
你应该去，我也会去的
You should go. And I'll go.
然后，那样的话，我们就可以一起了
And then, that way, we're kind of going together.
呃——
Uh--
- 嗯？ - 嗯，好吧
- Huh? - Uh, okay.
我现在得上厕所
I have to bathroom now.
- 哦 - 我的天啊
- Oh. - Oh, my God.
请忘记我刚才说的话
Please forget I just said that.
哦
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
别担心，我把它从我的记忆中清除了，所以...
Don't worry, I flushed it from my memory, so...
也许昨晚不该吃那块奶酪
Probably shouldn't have eaten that block of cheese last night.
我勒个去？
What the hell?
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
别是今天
Not today.
来吧，进来吧
STUDENT 1: Come on, get in here.
我可以推荐男卫生间吗？
May I suggest the boys' room?
男人已经夺走了女人很多东西
Men have taken so much from women already.
女孩不拉屎，笨蛋
STUDENT 1: Girls don't poo-poo, dumbass.
老天，我讨厌书呆子。
God, I hate nerds.
本尼根  - 我也是
Bennigan. STUDENT 2: Me too.
我妈妈为了一个书呆子离开了我棒极了的爸爸
My mom left my awesome dad for a nerd.
现在我们参观历史悠久的桥梁，而不是看足球比赛
Now instead of football games, we visit historical bridges.
桥梁？恶心！
Bridges? Gross!
现在让我们直播你
STUDENT 2: Now let's get you on my livestream
让每个人都能看到你流血
so everyone can watch you bleed.
啊，这感觉就像从冲马桶来了个大升级，伙计
Ah, this feels like a big escalation from swirlies, man.
但我们今年毕业，我们的暴力也是
But we graduate this year, and so should our violence.
嘿，嘘
STUDENT 2: Hey, shh.
你听到那滴滴答答的声音了吗？
You hear that drippy drip?
那可不是漏水的水龙头
That ain't no leaky faucet.
- 啊！ - 哦，是一个怪异的新女孩
- Ah! - Oh, it's a freaky new girl.
我想我对她们
STUDENT 1: Guess I was wrong
不拉屎的想法是错的
about them not poo-pooing.
不，伙计  那不是大便
Nah, dude. That's no dookie.
怪异的新女孩成长为怪异的新女人
Freaky new girl's blossomed into freaky new woman.
拜托不要
Please don't.
向世界问好，血腥玛丽
Say hi to the world, Bloody Mary.
你听到我说什么了吗？
STUDENT 1: You hear what I said?
你因为她有月经污渍
STUDENT 2: You called her Bloody Mary
叫她血腥玛丽
'cause she's got her period stain.
啊，他的腿！
Aah, his legs!
哇偶
Whoa.
我不是暴力支持者
I'm not a proponent of violence,
但这无疑是一种宣泄
but that was irrefutably cathartic.
- 那么
- So-- - So...
那么关于那个派对，那个邀请还是——
So about that party, is that invite still--
- 是的！ - 哦！
- Yes! - Oh!
- 是的  - 太棒了
- Yes. - Sweet.
- 很好 - 那太棒了
- Great. - That's great.
到时见  - 好的
See you at there then. - Cool.
有序离开大楼！
Exit the building in an orderly fashion!
我说有序！
I said orderly!
妈妈？
Mom?
快进来 快点
Get in now. Come on.
这儿 这儿
Here, here.
给你的头发上撒盐，然后烧掉这张你自己的照片
Salt your hair and burn this photo of yourself.
什么？为什么？发生了什么？
What? Why? What's happening?
听着，我很抱歉拖到现在
Look, I'm sorry for putting this off.
你爸爸是魔鬼
Your dad is the Devil,
而你是他通往地球的致命通道
and you're his mortal conduit to Earth,
圣经所称的敌基督者
known to Bible-y types as the Antichrist.
什么鬼？
What the fuck?
你来了月经，在天上开了个洞
You got your period and made that hole in the sky,
现在你爸爸知道在哪里可以找到你，所以我们得走了
and now your dad knows where to find you, so we got to go.
但你说我爸爸死了
But you said my dad was dead.
我说不是活的 系好安全带，亲爱的
I said not alive. Fasten your seatbelt, honey.
如果你对女性卫生有任何疑问
And if you have any questions about feminine hygiene,
枪下面的杂物箱里有一本小册子
there's a pamphlet in the glovebox right under the gun.
枪？
Gun?
那是一只勇敢的鹦鹉
That's one brave parakeet.
- 希望他远离推特
- Hope he stays off Twitter.
来看看其他新闻，当地一所初中的天空
In other news, the sky over a local junior high
被撕开了
has torn open,
在米德尔敦上空留下一个宇宙黑洞
leaving a cosmic black void over Middletown.
当局没有关于黑洞起源
REPORTER 1: Authorities have no details
或目的的详细说明
about the black hole's origin or purpose.
但不管它想要什么
REPORTER 2: But whatever it wants,
你可以打赌它不会
you can bet it won't
阻止我们参加谢拉·罗森布拉特
be keeping us from Shayla Rosenblatt's
在康科德派克废弃的塔科城堡
birthday after-party
举行的生日派对
at the abandoned Taco Chateau on Concord Pike.
接下来是访问好莱坞
Access Hollywood is next.
让他接电话
Put him on.
教皇
The Pope.
你这个愚蠢的家伙
You goofy rascal.
你自己接电话？
You answer your own phone?
黑洞来了
The black hole has arrived.
是我挫败撒旦邪恶计划的时候了
The time has come for me to thwart Satan's fiendish plan
通过杀死他的后代，敌基督
by killing his spawn, the Antichrist.
我们说话的时候，我的部队正在米德尔敦集结，然后——
My forces assemble in Middletown as we speak, and--
有人在敲门？
someone's beeping in?
哦，不 请应门吧
Oh, no. Please grab it.
孩子死后我会打电话给你的
I'll call you when the child is dead.
全都拿走吧！
Take it all!
我喜欢事物本来的样子
I liked things the way they were.
我应该接受你和撒旦或任何人
I'm supposed to accept that you had sex with Satan,
上过床？
or anyone?
哈，严重灼伤！
Ha, tight burn!
事实上，克丽丝，所有的女人曾经都是女孩
Fact, Chrissy, all women were girls.
所有的女孩都会做出选择，其中一半的选择是坏的
All girls make choices, and half of those are bad.
那么——那么八年搬家14次不是为了工作吗？
So--so moving 14 times in eight years wasn't for work?
不，是为了让你爸爸无法追踪我们
No, it was so your dad couldn't track us,
除了我们离开佛蒙特州那次
except when we left Vermont.
我应对不了那些该死的嬉皮士
I cannot deal with those fucking hippies.
听着，我试图给你
Look, I was trying to give you
一些正常的童年时光
some glimmer of a normal childhood.
好吗？ - 正常？
Okay? - Normal?
我的生活没有什么正常的！你是精神病吗？
Nothing's normal about my life! Are you mental?
我没有朋友，刚刚还炸了两个恶霸！
I have no friends, and I just exploded two bullies!
恶霸？克里斯蒂娜，他们伤害了你吗？
Bullies? Did they hurt you, Christina?
因为如果他们这样做了，我向上帝发誓——
Because if they did, I swear to God--
他们死了！
They're dead!
好吧，他们死了，是的
Okay, they're dead, yes,
但在这个家庭里，我们不会沉溺于过去
but in this family, we don't dwell on the past.
我们展望未来，我们的未来是在
We look to the future, and in our future,
阿拉斯加的一个因纽特人渔村
there's an Inuit fishing village in Alaska
那里非常遥远，会让怀俄明州的鬼城
that's so remote, it'll make that ghost town in Wyoming
看起来像上海  - 不，不，这次不要
look like Shanghai. - No, no, not this time.
不，我交了我的第一个朋友，他是个男孩
No, I made my first friend, and he's a boy,
他邀请我参加我的第一次派对
and he invited me to my first party.
你的阴道刚刚变成
And your vagina just became
黑暗王子的导航设备
a homing device for the Prince of Darkness.
我爸爸不是那个一辈子
My dad's not the one who's been gaslighting me
都在给我加油的人
my entire life.
也许我想让他找到我
Maybe I want him to find me.
哦，你最好仔细考虑一下你说的下一个词
Oh, you better choose your next words carefully.
来找我，撒旦！
Come and get me, Satan!
哦，那就是我不想让你说的！
Oh, that is what I didn't want you to say!
我们收拾行李，然后离开  - 你离我远点
We're packing, then leaving. - Get off of me.
哦，嘿，劳尔，我把你的糖留在了邮箱里
Oh, hey, Laur, I left your sugar in the mailbox.
哦，天啊，你觉得这是怎么回事，嗯？
Oh, God, what do you make of this thing, huh?
圣经还是媒体？
Biblical or the media?
你永远不知道现在的日子会发生什么，达琳
You never know these days, Darlene.
是的，你永远不知道，不是吗？
Yeah, you never do know, do you?
你什么都不知道……放开我！
You don't know anything... Let go of me!
直到你知道为止  - 你离我远点！
Until you know it. - Get off of me!
然后你不——过来！
And then you don't-- - Come on!
啊!  -过来
Ah!  -Come on.
不！ - 过来
No! - Come on.
天啊！你告诉我的一切都是谎言
God! Everything you ever told me is a lie.
我撒谎是为了保护你，我一点也不后悔
I lied to protect you, and I don't regret it for a second.
我唯一需要被保护远离的就是你
The only thing I need protection from is you.
哦，没有我你就不会在世界上活着了
Oh, you wouldn't last a day in the real world without me.
你是个婊子！
You're a bitch!
而你是个忘恩负义的混蛋
And you're an ungrateful asshole.
烧得好
Touché.
现在换裤子，甜心
Now change your pants, sweetheart.
你上了魔鬼
You banged the Devil
因为他是唯一一个会和你在一起的人
'cause he's the only one who would actually go there.
该死的，我应该这么对她说的
Damn, that's what I should have said to her.
我们可以带你离开这里
We can take you away from here.
首先，你必须同意见你父亲
First, you must agree to see your father.
哦，我爸派你来的？
Oh, my dad sent you?
如果我同意见他，我可以搭个车去
If I agree to do that, can I get a ride
康科德派克废弃的塔可城堡吗？
to the abandoned Taco Chateau on Concord Pike?
那不成问题
That would not be an issue.
事实上，我们无权
Actually, we are not authorized
作出承诺
to make that promise,
但没有什么是不可能的
but nothing is off the table.
你父亲会很乐意提供的
Your father is well able to provide.
好  我同意见我父亲
Okay. I agree to see my father.
哇！- 我不知道
Whoa! - I will not learn
他们的名字，但你可以带一个——
their names, but you can bring one--
打完了吗？
Finished?
还差点，最后一颗子弹是银的
Almost. Last one's silver.
不！
No!
该死的！
Damn it!
啊。
Ugh.
啊——
Aah--
不！
no!
除非你看着我，否则你不能砸碎我
You're not smashing me until you look at me.
看着我！
Look at me!
一坨屎
Piece of shit.
你装腔作势，巫术荡妇
You poser, Wiccan slut.
如果你操了魔鬼，现在举起你的手
Now raise your hand if you fucked the Devil.
如果你知道这一天会来，保持举手
Now keep your hand up if you knew this day was coming.
现在让我们去粉碎一些狗屎去改变现状
Now let's go smash some shit that makes a difference.
祝你好运 闭嘴，欧文
Good luck. Shut up, Irwin.
看来黑洞已经停止吸收了
It appears the black hole has stopped sucking.
一些吹毛求疵的科学家说
Some fact-thumping scientist said
这个洞会永远吸收下去
that this hole will suck forever.
真他妈的笑话
What a fucking joke.
现在，让我们今晚在谢拉·罗森布拉特的
Now let's rock it out tonight
生日派对上尽情狂欢吧
at Shayla Rosenblatt's birthday after-party!
我是房地产检查员 你呢？
Real estate inspector. How about yourself?
我为普世教会的最高教皇
I purge the world of demonic forces
清除世界上的恶魔势力
for the supreme pontiff of the universal church.
出差？还是出来玩？
Business trip? Pleasure?
他们说做你爱做的事
They say do what you love.
我最爱的莫过于为了钱
And I love nothing more than cutting out the heart
而割下一个少女的心脏
of an adolescent girl for monetary gain.
把女孩换成石膏板，心脏换成模型损坏
Swap girl with drywall and heart with mold damage,
我们的工作基本上是一样的
and we basically have the same job.
我想她妈妈杀了他
I think her mother killed him.
他是我们中最出色的，但我们必须继续前进
He was the best of us, but we must move on.
这是它所希望的
It's what would have wanted.
然后她说，“我撒谎是为了保护你”
And she says, "I lied to protect you."
- 她听起来像个婊子。 - 我就是那么说的
- She sounds like a bitch. - That's what I said.
嗯？
Huh?
这一刻从时间之初
It's been prophesized
就被预言了 呜！
since time began. Whoo!
现在，他们终于联合了
And now, they are finally united,
将在剩下的时间里
the dastardly duo
改变宇宙的卑鄙二人组
who will alter the universe for the rest of time.
来你父亲这里，达米安
Come to your father, Damien.
没有达米安的感觉
Not getting a Damien vibe.
哦，你是个女孩
Huh, you're a girl.
未来是女性的！
The future is female!
我支持并相信你
I support and believe you.
等等，等下，你会更喜欢这件男士西装的
Wait, hold on, you'll like this man suit better.
恭喜你流下了第一滴血！
Congrats on shedding first blood!
哇！大家能不要再谈论我的经期了吗？
Ew! Can everyone please stop talking about my period?
天啊 不，恶心
Oh, God. No, gross.
是你妈妈告诉你的吗？
Did your mom tell you that?
我说的是你谋杀的青少年
I'm talking about the teens you murdered.
- 我不是故意的  - 不要让别人的
- I didn't mean to. - Don't let other people's
道德法则让你认为你的所作所为是错误的
moral laws make you think what you did was wrong.
你和我可以一起创造一个没有规则的未来
Together, you and I can create a future without rules,
在那里你可以自己决定
where you can call your own shots,
过你想要过的生活
live the life you want to live.
有什么想法吗？ - 是的，我有想法
Thoughts? - Yeah, I've got thoughts.
我这一生你都去哪儿了？
Where have you been my whole life?
我有什么你突然想要的？
And what do I have that you suddenly want?
宝贝，我不是一个无赖爸爸 你被偷走了
Baby, I'm not a deadbeat dad. You were stolen.
在你获得你的能力前我找不到你
And I couldn't find you until you came into your powers.
我无法打破这些该死的宇宙法则
There are these fucking cosmic laws I can't break.
这就是我不在地狱的原因
That's why I'm not in hell.
- 等等，这不是地狱吗？ - 妈的，不是
- Wait, this isn't hell? - Shit, no.
这是玄幻领域
This is the metaphysical realm.
嗯， 真想不到
Hmm, fancy.
嬉皮士称之为边缘
Hipsters call it the Fringe,
让我想在我的脸上开个洞
which makes me want to punch a hole in my face.
它就像所有超自然领域的中心枢纽
It's like the central hub for all unearthly realms.
想想港务局
Think port authority,
但是有很多很多很多的尿液
but with much, much, much more urine
和更少的炸弹威胁
and fewer bomb threats.
所以如果我发号施令
So if I call the shots,
是不是意味着我不必听任何人的话？
does that mean I don't have to listen to anyone?
看那个家伙
Look at that guy.
他有一个鸟头，还会拉泡泡
He's got a bird head, and he craps bubbles.
我觉得这很酷
I thought that was pretty cool.
顺便问一下，你叫什么名字？
What's your name, by the way?
克里斯蒂娜
Christina.
她当然给你起了这个名字
Course she named you that.
之后我说，“哦，好吧，朗达
And I'm like, "Oh, okay, Rhonda,
“所以你是说黑洞是你丈夫
"so you're saying a black hole's the reason
出轨三年的原因？”
your husband's been cheating on you for three years?"
哦，嘿，你有跟
Oh, hey, did you get in touch
我介绍的那个人联系吗，埃里克？
with that guy I told you about, Eric?
他又贴心又富有，还是一位老年心理学家
He's sweet and rich and a geropsychologist.
相比于谈恋爱
Yeah, I'd rather fist a dog
我更愿意打狗，达琳
than be in a relationship, Darlene.
小羊皮？你是什么人，德鲁伊吗？
Lambskin? What are you, a druid?
你真复古
You're so retro.
哦，不过在今晚谢拉·罗森布拉特的
Oh, but that should come in handy tonight
生日派对上应该能派上用场
for Shayla Rosenblatt's birthday after-party.
我带了果冻
I'm bringing frosé.
你上当了！
Whoo, you're jacked!
说真的，你的身体看着像罪犯
Seriously, you got the body of a convict.
哦，你用它来储存
Oh, and you use it for storage.
我要进入玄幻领域
I'm going into the metaphysical realm
去杀死魔鬼并把我的女儿带回来
to kill the Devil and get my daughter,
我需要你在我离开的时候看着我的身体
and I need you to watch my body while I'm gone.
如果成功的话...-哦，哇
If this works... -Oh, wow.
我看起来会像死了一样，好吗？
I'm gonna look like I'm dead, okay?
但是理论上讲，我不会死
But technically, I won't be.
如果没有成功，我看上去就死了
If it doesn't work, I will just look and be dead.
天啊 你知道你在做什么吗？
Jesus. Do you know what you're doing?
好吧，但是你什么时候回来？
Okay, but when are you coming back?
好吧 好的 我就在这里等着
Okay. All right. I'll just wait here.
- 啊--
- Ah--
苦难滋养了我们猪的高潮
（粗略翻译）
天哪，疼死了
Holy shit, that was painful.
追踪！
大家 这是我的女儿
Hey, everybody. This is my daughter.
拍她的马屁，否则我会杀光你的孩子
Kiss her ass, or I'll slaughter your children.
- 为你感到骄傲！ - 嘿，我们喝一杯
- Proud of you! - Hey, let's have a drink.
我知道，现在你在想
I know, now you're thinking,
他是爸爸还是只是一个很酷的朋友？
is he a dad or just a cool friend?
我在想你过于努力了
I was thinking that you're trying too hard.
那是轨道灯吗？
Is that track lighting?
我们还在——这是一项正在进行的工作
We're still-- it's a work in progress.
臂蛇，来一轮辛辣的
Snake with Arms, a round of something spicy.
说到辛辣，你妈妈怎么样？
Speaking of spicy, how's your mom?
她还是个酒鬼吗？ - 嗯？
Is she still an alcoholic? - Huh?
- 她曾经搞过一盏灯。 - 我对此不感兴趣
- She fucked a lamp once. - I'm not interested--
等等，什么？ - 听着，她不理解你
wait, what? - Look, she doesn't get you.
我理解你 你是一个青少年
I do. You're a teen.
你不应该在逃亡中生活
You shouldn't be living on the lam.
你应该扎下根来，做正常青少年做的事
You should be planting roots, doing normal teen things.
真的吗？酷，因为你派来的
Really? Cool, because the beast guys
怪兽们说你会
you sent said you'd be down
送我去废弃的——
to give me a ride to the abandoned--
废弃的塔可城堡？ 嘣！
The abandoned Taco Chateau? Blam-o!
哇，你其实还挺好的
Wow, you're actually kind of okay.
出发前干个杯
A toast before you head out.
为我了不起的女儿
To my frickin' amazing daughter.
哦，好的，谢谢，爸爸
Oh, well, thanks, Dad.
为了你的未来
To your future,
并同意以父系和后裔的身份加入
and to consenting to join as sire and seed,
夺回地狱的主权——
reclaiming the infernal sovereign--
- 啊，就是这样  - 什么？
- Ah, there it is. - What?
你差劲的想把我困在你有约束力的协议里
Your lame attempt to trap me in your binding agreement.
哦，不，不  一点也不差劲
Oh, no, no. It's not lame at all.
它叫做大黎明
It's called Maximus Dawnus.
当我们一起执行它时
And when we carry it out together,
它会让我们把所有的领域
it'll let us fold all the realms
都合并成一个更强大的无法无天的大宇宙
into one big, way more powerful, lawless universe.
就像一个无政府主义的社会主义乌托邦
It'll be like an anarchistic socialist utopia.
听起来很酷，对吧？ - 嗯哼
That sounds cool, right? - Uh-huh.
妈妈？
Mom?
还记得我吗，混蛋？
Remember me, motherfucker?
- 我怎么能忘呢？ - 妈妈，你怎么--
- How could I forget? - Mom, how did you--
你胖了——好的那种，好的那种
You bulked up-- in a good way, in a good way.
13年来一直在为这一天做准备
13 years preparing for the day
这个腐坏的拙男将发挥他的作用并连接我们的世界
this rotting chode would make his play and bridge our worlds.
欢迎你给你比在浸过龙舌兰酒的卫生棉条里的
You're welcome for giving you a higher calling
机器人撕裂更高的呼召
than robotripping in tequila-soaked tampons.
这话来自于一个假装成别人
Coming from a guy who pretended
天杀的六个月的家伙
to be someone else for six goddamn months.
你惹错了婊子
You gaslit the wrong bitch.
脑部中枪
Brain shot.
解决它，妹子
Get it, girl.
头部粉碎 - 我的天啊
Head smash. - Oh, my God.
你是谁？
Who are you?
- 去你的
- Fuck you.
你觉得你要怎么做，杀了我？
What do you think you're gonna do, kill me?
我不是德古拉 我是该死的魔鬼
I'm not Dracula. I'm the goddamn Devil.
你最多只能对我指手画脚就像——
You got about as much chance of laying a finger on me as--
- 哦！那是什么？
- Ow! What was that?
未受割礼的卡巴里教徒
Oil of Abramelin
赐福的阿布拉梅林油
blessed by an uncircumcised Kabbalist rabbi.
- 什么？ - 妈妈！
- What? - Mom!
如果他认为那很疼
And if he thought that hurt,
那他会喜欢这个
he's gonna love this
塞进他鸡巴的山羊角的！
goat's horn shoved up his dick!
救命！杀了她！
Help! Kill her!
哦，真是个该死的女人
Oh, what a fucking woman.
你不是要把什么东西塞进我的鸡巴吗？
Weren't you about to shove something up my dick?
没人能告诉妈妈该做什么
No one tells Mama what to do.
啊
Ugh.
你是一个为了让自己再次强大起来
You're a washed-up, desperate con artist
而乞求一个小女孩签署愚蠢协议
begging for a little girl to sign his stupid pact
的彻底失败的绝望骗子
to make him feel big again.
不，不，不，不，不，不 不要鸡巴洞
No, no, no, no, no. No dick hole.
你想谈谈绝望？
You want to talk about desperation?
不要让母亲的职责影响你的头脑
Don't let the job of mother go to your head.
你为了养育我的后代而放弃了你的人生
You left your whole life behind to raise my spawn.
- 爸爸，停下！ - 你没什么特别的
- Dad, stop! - You're nothing special.
你只是一个容器  嘿？
You're just a vessel. Hello?
有人听我说话吗？
Does anyone even hear me?
你认为我觉得自己很独特？
You think I felt special?
你的魔法精液毁了我的生活 你应该庆幸我没有杀了它
Your magic jizz ruined my life. You're lucky I didn't kill it.
你应该庆幸它被你
You're lucky it didn't kill itself,
束缚了13年
being shackled to you
还没有自杀 去他的吧
for 13 years. Fuck this.
好吧，一旦她了解了你
Well, once she gets to know you,
我相信她会抓住机会
I'm sure she'll jump at the chance
割你的腕
to slit your wrists.
我不流血，婊子
I don't bleed, bitch.
恶心的父母 他们根本不在乎我
Gross-ass parents. They don't care about me.
好吧，我也不在乎他们
Well, I don't care about them.
实际上，我什么都不在乎
Actually, I don't care about anything.
为我操蛋的父母干杯
A toast to my parents for fucking me up, huh?
好响
PARTY GUEST 1: That slaps.
新来的女孩正在为这个派对增添乐趣
New girl is spicing this party up.
我们喜欢你不在乎别人的想法
We love that you don't care what anyone thinks.
太迷人了，亲爱的
Slay, honey.
我会迷死人的
Slay I shall.
本尼！本尼根，嘿！
Benny! Bennigan, hey!
克丽丝！哇，你真来了
Chrissy! Wow, you made it.
- 哈！ - 你杀了那两个恶霸
- Ha! - You left so quickly
后走的太快了
after you murdered those two bullies,
我还没有机会谢谢你
I never got a chance to thank you.
所以谢谢你  - 不用谢
So thank you. - Pssh, no thanks necessary.
衷心的
Totes my pleash.
我希望你今天剩下的时间里爆炸少些
I hope the rest of your day was less explosive.
是的，没错，除非你算上我自制的松饼
Yep, it was, unless you count the explosion of flavor
的香味爆炸
in my homemade muffins. Oh!
但那只是在字面意义上
But in a more literal sense,
不，只有那一次爆炸
no, it was just that one explosion.
你怎么样？ - 有些大起大落
You? - Some ups, some downs.
你知道吗，我刚刚发现我爸爸并没死
You know, I just found out my dad's not really dead.
我妈妈一点也不在乎我
My mom doesn't give two shits about me.
在过去的13年里
The last 13 years of my life,
我一直是他们糟糕关系中的一个棋子
I've been a pawn in their fucked-up relationship.
我坐着一辆
I rode on a carriage
由两只变异海妖的血肉变成的马车来到这里
made from the flesh of two mutated krakens to get here,
我希望我从未出生
and I wish I was never born.
但除了这些之外，这是美好的一天
But otherwise, a great day.
好吧，如果我可以许一个愿，我会取消你的愿望
Well, if I had a wish, I'd cancel your wish
因为我觉得你出生真是太好了
because I think it's pretty great you were born.
哦 谢谢你，本尼根
Aw. Thanks, Bennigan.
- 你感觉好点了吗？ - 好的不能更好了
- You feeling better? - Better than better.
我是他妈的敌基督！
I'm the motherfucking Antichrist!
听好了，别在面包车里留下垃圾
Listen carefully, do not leave your trash in this van.
这是租来的
It is a rental.
现在，我们来把这个孩子开肠破肚
Now, let's gut this child
然后把他的内脏像围巾一样戴在脖子上
and wear her entrails as a scarf.
我当初应该选你的妓女妹妹
I should have chosen your whore sister.
哦，操
Oh, fuck.
等一下 暂停
Hold up. Time out.
看
Look.
克丽丝是怎么回到地球的？
How did Chrissy get back to Earth?
那不是问题所在 这才是
That's not the problem. This is.
这些混蛋是被雇佣来处理恶魔的雇佣兵
These asshats are mercenaries hired to dispose of demons.
如果我们不阻止他们，他们会杀了克丽丝
They're gonna kill Chrissy if we don't stop them.
“我们”？去你的
"We"? Fuck you.
为了我们的女儿
Let's stop measuring dicks
停止打架吧
for our daughter's sake.
我需要一具尸体，但要新鲜的
I need a cadaver, but fresh,
在手指抽搐和肠道释放之间的那种
like between a finger twitch and a bowel release.
等一下，我们约会的时候
Wait a minute, when we dated,
你是在别人的尸体里吗？
were you inside someone's corpse?
你还有一个未完成的海豚纹身呢
And you had an unfinished dolphin tattoo.
不要那么势利
Don't be a snob.
杰拉德会参加那个派对
Gerald's gonna be at that party,
我不管他是不是刚做了膝盖手术
and I don't care if he just had knee surgery
因为我就要打的他去做了！
'cause I'm about to hit that!
- 天啊！
- Oh, my gosh!
欢迎回来 你应该洗个澡
Well, welcome back. You should take a shower.
你闻起来像腐烂了一样
You smell like rot.
我到底要去哪里找尸体？
Where the hell am I gonna find a cadaver?
劳拉，我只能为你做这么多了
There's only so far I'll go for you, Laura.
派对上见
I'll see you at the party.
好吧，他最好也有健康保险
Okay, he better have health insurance too
因为我要撕碎它
'cause I'm gonna tear that back up.
哦，天啊​​，小心点！
PARTY GUEST 1: Oh, God, watch out!
这是斗篷季还是什么别的？
PARTY GUEST 2: Is it, like, cloak season or something?
往前推
PARTY GUEST 3: Push your way to the front.
我们终于见面了，邪恶的野兽
At last we meet, vile beast.
我整个生涯都在等着
I've waited my entire career
看着生命从你丑陋的眼睛中流逝
to watch the life drain from your hideous eyes
并终结你父亲的计划
and put an end to your father's plan.
派对嘉宾 1：找份正经工作！ - 我的薪水很高！
PARTY GUEST 1: Get a real job! - I am well paid!
我想你不知道你在和谁打交道，领头的
I don't think you know who you're dealing with, Chief.
快点小便 你的裤子着火了
Piss quick. Your pants are on fire.
哦哦哦！
Oh, oh, oh!
如果你有烟就抽吧
Smoke if you got 'em.
这是给你的，狗崽子
Here you go, Sparky.
点起火来，宝贝！
Fire it up, baby!
我勒个去？
What the hell?
这是什么？
What is this?
现在，真正的痛苦开始了
And now, the real suffering begins.
- 放开她！ - 本尼根
- Leave her alone! - Bennigan.
我有一种我会没事的直觉
I have a gut feeling I'll be okay.
这个派对真是糟透了
PARTY GUEST 4: This party just got lame.
欺骗者，黑暗者，
Deceiver, dark one,
你将被打入……
thou shall be cast into...
哇，对不起
Wow, sorry.
这就像，你和这个敌基督
It's like, you stand here
在这里，手里拿着仪式用的刀
holding the ceremonial knife with this Antichrist--
谁他妈在乎？
PARTY GUEST 5: Who gives a shit?
我在乎
I do.
我是你的最终审判
And I am your final judgment.
为什么？
Why?
喜剧性
Comedy.
把手从我女儿身上拿开
Get your hands off my daughter.
我们的女儿  - 哦，棒极了
Our daughter. - Oh, great.
我的父母在这里
My parents are here.
嗨，亲爱的 我现在是一只鸡
Hi, honey. I'm a chicken now.
噢！
HENCHMAN 2: Ow!
啊！
HENCHMAN 3: Aah!
哦！
HENCHMAN 4: Oh!
我在流血，我在流血
HENCHMAN 5: I'm bleeding, I'm bleeding.
真的吗，你就会这些？
Really, that's all you got?
我让十几个家伙把他们的鸡巴都打掉了
I made a dozen guys shoot their dicks off.
还有一个阴道！
PARTY GUEST 6: And one vagina!
哇！
Whoo!
现在，我们玩得很开心
Now, we're having fun.
我们就像超人总动员，但是是恶心版的
We're like The Incredibles but gross.
- 让我用我最后一口气，让 -
- With my last breath, let--
我会报仇的 你会付出代价的！
I will get my revenge. You shall pay!
有人看到我鸡巴的前端了吗？
Has anyone seen the tip of my dick?
如果我的父母出现在派对上
If my parents ever show up to a party,
用刀杀了我
murder me with a knife.
除了西西弗斯假装喜欢巨石
What is middle school
中学是什么？
but Sisyphus pretending to love the boulder?
明天在山脚下见，新来的女孩
See you at the bottom of the hill tomorrow, new girl.
- 那太高深了  - 我姐姐有西西弗斯
- That was so deep. - My sister had Sisyphus.
明天见！
See you tomorrow!
伙计，我们有一个奇怪的见面，对吧？
Boy, did we have a meet-weird, right?
就像是一个可爱的见面
Like it was a meet-cute,
但因为大屠杀而变得奇怪！
but it was weird 'cause of all the carnage!
克丽丝，你受伤了吗？
Chrissy, are you hurt?
不要担心 爸爸来了
Don't worry. Daddy's here.
哦，我会让你知道我会对爸爸做什么的
Oh, I'll show you what I do to Daddy.
都他妈的住手！
Just fucking stop it!
这是我生命中最糟糕的一天
This was the worst day of my life,
因为你们两个以自我为中心的混蛋
and it was because of you two self-centered assholes.
如果你想要你的父系和后裔或者别的什么
If you want your sire and seed or whatever
而你实际上想要一个女儿
and you actually want a daughter,
请知道我现在自己做主
know that I'm calling the shots now.
明白了吗？明白了吗？
Got it? Got it?
- 是的，明白了 冷静下来  - 是的，我们明白了
- Yeah, got it. Cool your jets. - Yeah, fine. We got it.
妈妈，我明天要去上学
Mom, I'm going to school tomorrow.
再也不逃跑了
No more running.
爸爸，我不相信你
And, Dad, I don't trust you,
但我想要了解你，但是要慢慢来
but I want to get to know you, but slowly,
比如每周末
like every other weekend.
每个周末？这有点薄弱
Every other? That's a little weak.
他妈的！
God damn it!
我们有时间谈判
We got time to negotiate.
现在，谁想吃煎饼？
Now, who wants pancakes?
好吧，现在你见过你父亲了
Well, now you've met your father.
我们能回家了吗？
不，还不能
No, not yet.
她妈妈比我想象的要强
Her mother's stronger than I thought.
但是，嘿，谁在乎呢？
But hey, who cares?
我女儿很快就会加入我
My daughter's gonna join me soon,
然后我将永远是万物主宰
and then I'll be top shit for eternity.
但我必须要有点耐心，明白吗？
But I just got to be patient, you know?
而我是一个有耐心的人
And I'm a patient guy.
我写了一本关于耐心的书
I wrote the book on patience.
我有的是时间
Got all the time in the world.
你让我很难过
我只是想告诉你我在之前是浴室水槽
Just wanted to let you know that I left some sanitary pads
的地方的旁边留了一些卫生巾
near where the bathroom sink used to be.
哦，嘿，关于我说过我的生活被毁了的那件事
Oh, and hey, that thing I said about my life being ruined,
在我有你之前，我是一团糟
I was a mess before I had you.
我就是这样有你的
That's sort of how I had you,
所以，你没有毁掉任何东西
so yeah, you didn't ruin anything.
你让我变得更好，好吗？
You made me better, okay?
我爱你 晚安
I love you. Night.
我的宝贝女儿长大了
My little baby girl is all grown up.
妈妈也该长大了
Time for Mama to grow up too.
不再逃跑了
No more running.
我从没想过
I never thought I'd hear
我会听到劳拉·范伯格说这种话
the Laura Feinberg say those words.
哦，当你从阴影中走出来的时候
Oh, it is creepy when you come out
真让人毛骨悚然，欧文
of the shadows like that, Irwin.
我不控制这里的灯光
I don't control the lighting in here.
是你控制的 你知道吗
You do. You know,
也许妈妈不是在逃避魔鬼
maybe Mama wasn't running from the Devil.
也许妈妈是逃避成为一个真正的妈妈
Maybe Mama was running from being a real mama.
嗯，好吧
Uh, okay.
所以如果妈妈不再逃跑，接下来要做什么？
So if Mama's not running, what's next on the docket?
我不知道
I don't know.
反正人们总是在郊区做些什么，对吧？
What do people do in the suburbs anyway, huh?
耙落叶? 开个读书俱乐部？
Rake leaves? Start book clubs?
走进大海淹死自己？
Walk into the ocean and drown themselves?
我是说...
I mean...
嘿  你想看空中监狱吗？
Hey. You want to watch Con Air?
你读懂了妈妈的心思
You read Mama's mind.